David Fernando Zuluaga

PERSONAL DATA

LOCATION: Cali, Colombia
PHONE: (+57) 3167073325
SKYPE: david_fza

GITHUB: github.com/dafer154

LINKEDIN: www.linkedin.com/in/davidfza25/

EMAIL: zuluaaristi@gmail.com

Software Engineer with 1+ years in software development with knowledge in Front-End Technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and React, and in Backend technologies such as Python, Django rest framework and PostgrestSQL, I also have experience in Database design and Service Oriented Architectures. Other skills include team work and learning by myself. Also, I am passionate about implementing new technologies and writing coding.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEB 2018 - AUG 2018

Fullstack Developer, CIER Sur(Univalle), Cali- Colombia PROJECTS: "GIMNASIO DE HABILIDADES"

Developer of the "Gimnasio de habilidades", a gamified system that allows students to reinforce knowledge of quantitative reasoning and critical reading. dThe employed technologies are: Python, Django rest framework for the manage of API, PostgrestSQL, Postman and the Frontend: Rect, CSS3, Javascript with interfaces responsives and adaptatives with Flexbox and @media

Nov 2017 - Feb 2018

Frontend Developer, CIER Sur(Univalle), Cali- Colombia

PROJECTS: "OBJETOS VIRTUALES DE APRENDIZAJE PARA EDUCACIÓN SUPERIOR"

Developer of "Objetos de aprendizaje", the following technologies: HTMl5, CSS3 with interfaces responsives and adaptatives with Flexbox and @media, Jquery and JavaScript.

DEC 2015- MAY 2016

Development analyst, Banco de Occidente, Cali- Colombia

PROJECTS: "UNIFICACION PSP-OCCIRED"

Member of the development team of the business banking unit, in charge of the PSP Occired project, managing services with SOAP UI, Managing of data base ORACLE, and control of logs of data through ESB(Bus enterprise service).

JUN 2015- DEC 2015

Trainee, Banco de Occidente, Cali- Colombia

PROJECTS: "SISTEMA DE CARTERA FACTORING"

Software tester, Evaluating the quality of the product. Performing the test summary. Identifying the scope of the test. Design and performing of test cases. Analyse of test results. Conducting time estimation on assigned projects. Elaboration and evaluation of a the test plan and a test strategy for the project. Recording and tracking identified issues.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2017 Gpa: 4.04/5.0 Eng. Software Engineering, Universidad del Valle, Cali-Colombia

Degree Project: "Herramienta web para visualización de material educativo en el aula de clase y evaluación continua.", (Educational Web Application, Django, Django-channels,

Django-tenant, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Agile Development, Software Testing) The application allows teacher to evaluate students performance on real time.

GPA: 4.02/5.0

TECHNOLOGIES AND SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python(Django), JavaScript, TypeScript, Java Front-end programming : React, Angular, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, Bootstrap.

Data base : PostgreSQL, MySQL. Source control : Git, GitHub, BitBucket

Languages: Spanish (Native), English (conversational)